wrestleandfuck.com 2012-04-15

# WRESTLEHARD.COM - Gay wrestling adult videos

I. Introduction 

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy policy discloses the information practices for http://www.wrestlehard.com, including the types of information we gather and track, how we use that information, and with whom we share it. The purpose of this policy is to let you know how we use your personal information before we collect it. We have tried to include a link to this policy on every page on which personal information is collected. We have also provided a number of links at the bottom of this page for those interested in learning more about privacy issues in cyberspace.

II. Information Collection and Management

i. Information we collect

"Personally identifiable information" is information that can be used to identify or contact you, such as your name, e-mail address, home or work address, or telephone number. We only have access to the personally identifiable information that you provide to us. For example, we cannot determine your e-mail address unless you provide it. We cannot gain access to other information on your computer. Those who visit only public areas of the Web site (such as the "guest tour") and who do not purchase goods or services do not need to, and generally do not, provide us with any personally identifiable information. Those who wish to join the site, however; or to purchase products or services or sign up for our mailing list, must provide us with enough information to enable us to process the requested transaction. This generally includes, at a minimum, personally identifiable information such as name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number. Members also select, and thereby provide, a username and password combination.

ii. How we use the information

Your personally identifiable information is used only to process the requested transaction, and occasionally to provide you with special offers from **RA Network** and others. On occasion, for example, we may send e-mails to introduce a product or service that we think will interest our subscribers. **RA Network** will never intentionally disclose any personally identifying information to any third party, unless we are compelled to do so by law (for example, in response to a subpoena or court order), or our obligation to maintain the privacy of your information has been waived or otherwise excused by you (for example, by your filing suit against us and asserting claims against which such information would be relevant in our defense). Please note that our lawyers, accountants, and/or vendors are not "third parties" for the purpose of this section to the extent that disclosure to them is necessary or desirable for the operation of our business.

iii. Opt-out policy

Because your personal information is required for us to provide services to you, you cannot opt-out of providing it and still receive those services. You can also opt-out of receiving promotional e-mailings by clicking on the help link in the footer, then clicking 'report a problem' on the right nav bar. (Note that by setting your e-mail preference to "No" you will not receive advertising and promotional e-mail, but you may from time to time receive e-mails in connection with billing and/or site administration. For more detailed instructions about changing your preferences and personal information, click here.

B. Interactive data

i. Information we collect

ColtStudio.com provides a number of features that allow members to communicate with each other, such as a message board and chat room ("interactive features"). Chat transcripts and message board postings are backed up periodically in connection with our routine server maintenance, and thus may be retained for an indeterminate time.

ii. How we use the information

Use of these interactive features is not monitored by **RA Network**. We do not use information posted on interactive features except as the author presumably intended, that is, as content on the Web site (and occasionally as food for thought). We do not share user submitted information with third parties, however, any information posted is visible to other members, and is vulnerable to being copied and/or redistributed by others. Members should use reasonable caution when disclosing any personally identifiable information in any online forum. We cannot be responsible for any damages incurred as a result of such disclosure, and use of the interactive services is at the member's own risk.

iii. Opt-out policy

Members must opt-in (for example, by participating in a chat) in order for us to collect this information.

C. Click-stream data

i. Information we collect

We also collect non-personally identifying information provided by your browser and/or our servers, such as the name and IP address of the domain from which you visited (if any), the amount of time you spent on each page and on the site as a whole, and the path you followed through the site. This sort of information is sometimes known as click-stream data.

ii. How we use the information

We use click-stream data in the aggregate to analyze trends and statistics and to help us understand how subscribers use our site. This allows us to identify areas and technologies that need improvement, and to provide appropriate bandwidth and technical support for areas that are growing. None of this information is reviewed at an individual level. From time to time we may share this aggregate statistical information with partners, suppliers and other third parties, but it will not include any personally identifiable information.

iii. Opt-out policy

Click-stream data is generated by your browser and our servers, and therefore you cannot opt-out of providing it. However, some of the privacy resources listed below may provide a partial solution by (for example) allowing you to cloak your IP address.

D. Cookies

i. Information we collect

We collect certain non-personally identifying information through the use of "cookies." A cookie is a small file that a Web site can send to your browser to be stored on your system. Some cookies are deleted when you end your online session ("session cookies"), while others may be stored on your computer indefinitely ("persistent cookies"). We use session cookies on this site to store information such as user login status (so that you aren't forced to enter your username and password on every page). These cookies expire automatically when you log out.

ii. How we use the information

We use the information stored in cookies to personalize your Web site experience and to manage your online session. The information in cookies is both set and read by our server and is not logged in the process. We do not share data that we collect from cookies with third parties.

iii. Opt-out policy

You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, many areas of the site will not function properly.

III. Related Issues

A. Information security

We are constantly striving to improve the security of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational measures, such as using encryption for transmission of credit card numbers, to help us keep your information secure. We will continue to implement additional security measures as new technologies emerge.

For all customer service, account access, billing and login issues.

**RA Network** does not use third-party services to provide banner advertising.

C. Children's data

**RA Network** ' Web sites are not directed towards children, and do not collect any data governed by the United States' Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).

D. Privacy technology

There are an increasing number of products and services are available to help protect your privacy while navigating the Web. See http://www.privacyalliance.org/resources/rulesntools.shtml for an overview of some of these tools. Please note that **RA Network** has not formally evaluated these tools and makes no representations or warranties about them.

E. Business relationships

This contains links to other Web sites. **RA Network** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. For example, credit card billing is provided by iBill. The privacy of information that you provide to those companies is governed by their respective privacy policies and not that of **RA Network.**

F. Notification of changes

This privacy statement was last updated on May 27, 2008. A notice will be posted on our web site for 30 days whenever this privacy statement is changed.

G. Questions regarding this statement

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to **RA Network** Privacy coordinator.
